So now that we have seen how we can crack Mifare classic card using only one manufacture key in this
video, we are going to see what if we have all the keys modified and we have changed all the manufacturer
keys.
So let's just start with prox Mk3.
So let's just connect our prox Mk3.
So it's connected.
Now let's just check out the Uid of this card.
Now.
So this is the new card.
Let's just check out all the keys.
So we'll run a check command as we did before, and we will run it with all unknown keys because we
don't know any keys.
Or here you can see it's saying no valid key found or zero key found.
So it's not able to find any manufacturer key.
So let's just run nested attack as well.
So we are going to run nested attack.
With all the unknown factors.
So it's not able to find any known case, as you are seeing over here.
Can't found any of the known keys, so it's not able to find any keys.
Let's just run a slow attack as well.
So it's still not able to find any keys.
So the bottom line is, if you have modified all the keys in all the sector trailers, the card gets
secured.
But if you forget to modify any of the keys and left any of the keys on the manufacture or transport
configuration, the card is still vulnerable.
So make sure you modify all the keys in all the sector trailers when you are programming mifare Classic
cards.
So in the next video, we are going to see how to clone cards.
So first we will crack a card.
Then we will clone the same card on magic cards.